MBORI TSEMZANG BRANDON NTUNYU

Douala-Bonaberi, Littoral-Cameroon

+237 674478246/675471282 | mboribrandon@gmail.com

CV PROFILE

Highly skilled full stack developer with 4 years' experience in coding with a passion of building innovative and user-friendly software solutions. Also, a driven and analytical digital marketer with about 2 years' experience understanding customer behavior and driven conversation.

PERSONAL INFORMATION -

Nationality : CameroonianDate of Birth : 31-07-2000

• Gender : Male

• Driver's License: Category B

Health : GoodCriminal Record: None

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

• **High Tech Training center** (on going)

Full-stack training 2023-2024

• IUGET-University, Douala

Diploma in Software Engineering 2020-2022

Bixo-Academy

Digital Marketing Course 2022

• Startup Academy

Digital Marketing Course 2022

- PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Media ads

Remote Web Developer and Digital Marketer 2022- Now

CBC College

Computer Science Teacher 2023-2024

• La Bonte College

Computer Science Teacher 2023-2024

• Suzanna Comprehensive High School

Computer Science Teacher 2022-2023

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React Js
- Next Js
- Node Js
- MySQL
- Digital Marketing Strategy
- Content Marketing
- Social Media Marketing
- Data-Driven Decision Making

PERSONAL STRENGTH

- Good Time Management
- Working well under Pressure
- Adapt Easily
- Fast Learner and Open to learn more in the field
- Speak and Write French and English Fluently
- Good Communication Skills